securetrading.net 2003-06-28

# SECURETRADING web site privacy statement

This privacy statement relates to the SECURETRADING web site at www.securetrading.com.

SECURETRADING is a payment service provider based in the United Kingdom. Our contact details for enquiries about privacy and data protection issues can be found at the foot of this page.

## ANONYMOUS ACCESS TO OUR WEB SITE

You can access our web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

Any information supplied by your web browser (such as IP addresses, browser details and page requests) may be logged in order to provide us with statistics about the performance and effectiveness of our web site, but we do not link this information to personal data about specific individuals collected by any other means.

We do not use cookies on our web site.

## DATA COLLECTION AND ITS PURPOSE

We collect personal data using HTML forms on our web site. Use of these forms is entirely voluntary on your part, so if you don't want us to hold any personal data about you, then please do not submit the forms. The personal data collected is:

  * Your name
  * Your company name
  * Your telephone number
  * Your email address

We collect this data for sales and marketing purposes. A member of our sales team may use it to contact you in the future. We do not collect or use this personal data for any other purpose, and we do not disclose this personal data to other commercial organisations.

## CONFIDENTIALITY

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to ensure that any personal data held under our control is protected from unauthorised access, unauthorised modification, unlawful destruction, accidental loss, improper use or improper disclosure. All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.

## YOUR RIGHT OF ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA

Your rights of access to any personal data that we hold about you are as set out in the Data Protection Act 1998 (United Kingdom), and are summarised below:

  * You can ask us whether we keep personal information about you by contacting our Data Protection Officer. Contact details can be found at the foot of this page.
  * You can request a readable copy of your personal data from our Data Protection Officer, although we may first require proof of your identity. We charge £10.00 for this service, to cover our administrative costs. We will send the data to you within forty days of receiving the fee and verifying your identity.
  * You may challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data correcteded, amended, completed or deleted.

For further information about your rights under the Data Protection Act 1998 visit the Information Commissioner's web site at [www.dataprotection.gov.uk](http://www.dataprotection.gov.uk/).

## CONTACT DETAILS

If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, or you want to enquire about or request a copy of any of your personal data held by us, please contact our Data Protection Officer using one of the following methods:

Email:

| 

---|---  
  
Phone:

| 

+44 (0) 1248 672000  
  
Post:

| 

European Support & Development Centre  
Parc Menai Business Park  
Bangor  
Gwynedd  
UNITED KINGDOM  
LL57 4BF  
  
If you are not satisfied with our response to your concern you may wish to contact the Information Commissioner. Contact details can be found on the web site at [www.dataprotection.gov.uk](http://www.dataprotection.gov.uk/).

See our payment service in action by donating at one of these charity sites

Click here to request an information pack containing further details about SECURETRADING and our services

Need help in setting up your e-commerce site? Search our database of developers who use ST's technology

In any commercial arena, you need to take care to avoid fraud, and e-commerce is no different. See our guidelines to combatting fraud here

See which shopping carts integrate with ST's technology

Click here to see a list of financial institutions with whom we work

Read some case studies of companies who use our service

How secure is your network? Let us test it with STindago
